病人∶我想说的是,如果我珍惜的老婆认为工作比我们的婚姻还重要的话,
Patient: All I'm saying is, that if my wife, the woman that I cherish,
那就让她去死.
thinks getting a job is more important than our marriage, let her die.
杰森∶拉佩克先生,你在想象一下,
Jason: Mr.Lapepki, think for just a moment,
这个女人和十多年前与你结婚的不是一样的吗.
isn't this woman the same person you married ten years ago.
病人∶不,她长胖了.
Patient: No, she's fat.
杰森∶难道她连做自己事业的权利都没有了吗?
Jason: But does she not also have a right to her own professional fulfillment?
病人∶哇,你是瞎搅和!
Patient: Wow, you're whipped!
杰森∶拉佩克先生,如果我可以的话,
Jason: Mr.Lapepki, let me share with you a personal anecdote, if I may;
我愿意跟你分享一个我自己的轶事;大约四年多前,我也遇见了类似的问题.
I was in a similar situation about four years ago.
病人∶啊,你老婆也想变胖了?哼!?
Patient: Ah, right, your wife was putting on the pounds too, huh?
杰森∶不,不.
Jason: No.No, but after fifteen years as a home-maker,
在做了 15年的家庭主妇后,她突然决定要重新开始她的事业,
she suddenly decided to resume her career, I couldn't believe it!
我简直是不能相信!我当然不想放弃我的工作而做居家男人!
I mean, I certainly didn't want to give up everything I'd worked for and
毕竟在家里接触到的病人不能和在外面接触到的相比较...啊,
come home!I mean,
除你以外.因此,
after all the patients that you deal with at a home practice,
我必须做出决定;什么排在第一,我的事业还是我的婚姻...
frankly aren't always that inter...Ah, with the exception of you.
我选择了回家.说实在的,
So, I had a decision to make; what came first, my career or my marriage...
I came home.And quite frankly, Mr.Lapepki, I couldn't be happier
这样,你还会觉得我是在瞎搅和吗?
Now, does that sound whipped to you?
病人∶你根本就是在撒谎!
Patient: You can put it on pumpkin pie!
杰森∶好吧,今天到此为止.
Jason: Alright, well that's our session for today.
我要把这个办公室改造一下,因此下星期要在另一个地址了.
I'll be remodeling this office, so next week will be at another address.
病人∶哦,一个真正的办公室,哈!
Patient: Oh, a real office, huh?
杰森∶这里就是一个真正的办公室拉佩克先生,我在这里工作.
Jason: This is a real office Mr.Lapepki, I do real work here.
病人∶我并非要侮辱你.我期待着变化.
Patient: I didn't mean to insult you.I welcome the change.
有真正办公室的心理学家会更...有趣.
Psychiatrists with real offices are so much more...interesting.
麦琪∶杰森,我回来了!
Maggie: Jason, I'm home!
病人∶她可以随时搅和我.
Patient: She could whip me anytime.
开萝尔∶本,我的薄烤饼是冷的.
Carol: Ben, my pancakes are cold.
本∶那就不要吃了.
Ben: So, sit on 'em.
迈克∶本,在我的薄烤饼里的黑色东西是什么?
Mike: Ben, what are these little black things in my pancakes?
本∶是没有腿的虫子.
Ben: The ones without legs are rasinettes.
开萝尔∶你再也不要煮早餐了!
Carol: You are never gonna cook breakfast again!
本∶正中我下怀.
Ben: That's my plan.
迈克∶本,你仅仅只看到了爸爸要在这里办公的负面效应.
Mike: Benny look, you are only seeing the downside of Dad going to work here.
现在,还存在着一个好处呢.
Now, there is an upside too.
妈妈要上班,
OK, with Mom at work and Dad safely out of the way all week,
爸爸也整星期的不会干扰你,你今天什么时候从学校回来...
when you get home from school today...
杰森∶你们必须表现得和有我监视你们的时候一样乖.
Jason: You will behave exactly as if I was watching your every move.
迈克∶太奇妙了,他居然说了我要说的话.
Mike: Isn't that crazy, the man read my mind.
杰森∶是.
Jason: Yeah.
麦琪∶我了多余的尿布,克莉丝不习惯看护.
Maggie: I bought extra diapers, Chrissy isn't used to day care.
杰森∶找来的人还没有来吗?我应该提前5分钟走.
Jason: Where is that contract?I should have left five minutes ago.
路上到处塞车还有收费站!
There's all that traffic and then the toll, oh!
麦琪,我要零钱付通行费.
Maggie, I'm gonna need exact change for the toll.
迈克∶让我给,爸爸.本给他一元.
Mike: Allow me Dad.Ben, give the man a Buck.
杰森:麦琪,快,你说过你要帮克莉丝拿些多余的尿布.
Jason: Maggie, come on, you said you'd get me some extra diapers for Chrissy.
麦琪∶我说过,杰森.你太紧张了.
Maggie: I did, Jason.You're nervous.
杰森∶好,我对变化还不是很适应.
Jason: Well, I'm not who's comfortable with change.
本∶把25美分找回给我哦.
Ben: Then give me my quarters back.
杰森∶我需要的所有东西都在家里了;我不需要去交易,
Jason: You know everything I need is right here at home;
我没有任何的阻碍……
I don't need to commute, and I don't have any interruptions...
本∶你要去看Operah..大家都知道,爸爸.
Ben: And you get to watch Operah.Everybody knows, Dad.
麦琪∶这些年来,你在家里工作,的确帮我了很大的忙.
Maggie: And all these years I thought you were doing me a big favour by working at home.
杰森∶我可不是喜欢吹嘘的人,但是我是!哦!终于来了!
Jason: Well, I'm not the kind of guy to bring it up, but I am!Oh finally!
本∶是.
Ben: Yep.
法兰克∶你好,我把我的卡车停在外面的前草坪上,但愿不会有事.
Frank: Hi, I'm err...I parked my truck out on the front lawn, I hope it's OK.
杰森:大家好.这是法兰克,他要来改造一下办公室.
Jason: Hey, everybody, this is Frank, he's gonna be remodeling the office.
法兰克:我的 BP不见了,我要呼一下试试看.
Frank: My beeper went off, I gotta call it in.
我听见 BP机在响了,在我的背后.
I heard the stinking beeper, get off my back will you.
哦!这里谁是麦琪马龙?
Oh, is any one of you named Maggie Malone?
麦琪∶我是.
Maggie: Yes.
Frank: Gail something or other, from Esquire magazine.Could you make it quick
麦琪∶我听到你的BP机在响了.格雷,
Maggie: I heard, your beeper went off.
我用我丈夫的电话打回给你吧?
Gail, can I call you right back on my husbands line?OK.
杰森∶法兰克,关于我的办公室……
Jason: Frank, about my office...
法兰克∶等一下.说吧,
Frank: Just a sec.Go ahead, talk, I can do two things at once.
我可以一心二用.有什么要求吗?有了确切的想法没有?
Is there anything you wanna have done?Any certain ideas?
杰森∶在我的头脑里只有一些很乱七八糟的想法.
Jason: Well just a few random thoughts off the top of my head really.
法兰克∶我应该让你走.好了,我还有其他的事情要处理.
Frank: I gotta let you go.Yeah, I got another one of those.
本∶(在他的脑海里)嗨!
Ben: (In his head) Hey, wait a second!
等等!我整个星期的下午都可以独占整间房子了.
I'm gonna have the whole house to myself, every afternoon for a whole week.
我伪装的真好.
It's a good thing I got a poker face.
麦琪∶相信我Gail,
Maggie: Believe me Gail,
我很愿意写文章但是城里的工作已经让我忙不过来了……
I would love to do the article but the keep me so busy in town...
杰森:把这些书架拿走就能腾出更多的地方工作……
Jason: Losing these bookshelves will open up a whole work space here and...
麦琪∶哦!杰森,我在给时尚先生打电话.
Maggie: Oh Jason, I'm on the phone with Esquire.
杰森∶亲爱的,我们不是已经订阅了足够的杂志吗?
Jason: Honey, don't we subscribe to enough magazines already?Oh!
哦!我们需要一段时间来好好研究计划.
Well we need some time to check these plans.
麦琪∶格雷,我不得不用另一部电话打给你.有点耐心.
Maggie: Gail, I have to try yet another phone.Be patient with me.
杰森:对不起.办公室需要变化.
Jason: Sorry.So, what this office really needs is just a new face!
要明白,
You know, I'd like to have an office that says "a professional psychiatrist
我想要我的办公室像专业心理学家工作的地方.专业的心理学家.
works here!" A professional psychiatrist, call me home!
本:爸爸,
Ben: Dad, I was just wondering,
我想知道你今晚什么时候回家.
about what time are you gonna get home tonight.
杰森∶我也不知道,本;如果我快点出门的话,
Jason: I dunno, Ben, if I don't get outta here soon,
我估计今天晚上我都不用回来了.
I may not be home at all.
本∶(在脑海里)不回来更好.在这种情况下,如果是迈克,他会干什么呢?
Ben: (In his head) This is better than I thought.
聚会!聚会!聚会!
What would Mike do in a situation like this?Party!Party!Party!
杰森∶你对这个办公室有什么看法吗?
Jason: I mean does this office say anything to you?
法兰克:还没看呢..
Frank: Not a peep.
麦琪∶抱歉,我没时间里写文章.
Maggie: Sorry, I have no time to write anything.Bye.
再见.你会相信我居然拒绝了一个决佳的自由职业者的机会!
Can you believe I had to turn down another terrific freelance assignment!
杰森∶你能相信,网状墙纸要3000多美元吗?
Jason: Can you believe, three thousand Dollars for textured walls!
麦琪∶,但是我现在有写好文章的机会,
Maggie: Sure, now that I'm being offered good articles to write,
我哪有时间去拿!
I'm too busy to take them!
杰森∶我对医科学校烦透了,居然发现最大的机会居然在订立合同上!
Jason: And now that I bothered with medical school,
哦!克莉丝,对不起,
I find out the big Bucks are in contracting!
没有你,爸爸就不能活下去了!
Oh Chrissy, I'm sorry, Daddy wouldn't leave without ya!
杰森∶别哭,宝宝.再见宝宝!!GOO,GOO!
Jason: Don't cry, baby.Bye bye baby!!Goo goo!
凯文∶你来早了,医生还没来.
Kevin: You're a little early, the doctor's not in yet.
杰森∶哦,他来了.
Jason: Oh, yes he is.
凯文∶他还没来.
Kevin: Sure he is.
杰森∶我是杰森西维尔,我会用比格曼医生的办公室……
Jason: Oh, I'm Jason Seaver, I'm gonna be in Dr.Bigman's office this..
凯文∶哦,我们都在等你来呢.我是凯文.
Kevin: Right, we were expecting you.I'm Kevin Randall.
杰森∶哦,我刚刚把我的女儿送到看护中心.
Jason: Hi.Oh, I was just putting my daughter in day care.
你有那些特长呢?
So, what's your area of expertise?
凯文∶编订,打字,速记.
Kevin: Filing, typing, steno.
杰森∶哦!那你就是秘书了?
Jason: Oh, you treat secretaries?
凯文∶我是秘书.事实上,我是你的秘书.
Kevin: I am a secretary.In fact, I'm yours.
杰森∶啊,男秘书!
Jason: Ah, a male secretary!That's kind of strangely...
有点点奇怪地……对了,我想去我的办公室看看,在哪里呢?
fascinating, as an idea, yes.Well, err...I'll be in my office, which is where?
保罗∶杰森西维尔,你个王八蛋!
Paul: Jason Seaver, you son of a gun!
杰森∶嘿!保罗!
Jason: Hey Paul!
保罗∶多久了?
Paul: How long's it been?
杰森∶一个星期.你上次还在我家吃过晚餐呢,记得吗?
Jason: About a week.You had dinner at my place, remember?
保罗∶哦!那我为什么要拥抱你?
Paul: Oh, then why am I hugging you?
杰森∶我也不知道,
Jason: Well, I don't know, you always do that when you see me;
你每次见到我的时候都会这样做;让我觉得很紧张.
it's starting to get on my nerves.
保罗∶看过你的办公室了没有?
Paul: Have you seen your office?
杰森:还没有.
Jason: No.
保罗∶让我带你去.
Paul: Then let me show you.
杰森:好呀.
Jason: Wow.
保罗∶对,就这里!
Paul: Yeah.Alright!
杰森∶男秘书?!
Jason: A male secretary?!
保罗∶你的思想落伍了,Jase.
Paul: Come on!Where have you been, Jase?
杰森∶只是因为我从来没有过腿毛比我还多的秘书!也许曾经用过,
Jason: Well, it's just that I've never had a secretary with hairier legs
不过不是一码事.
than mine!Once maybe, but that's another story.
我真地不得不感谢你和菲尔,能让我使用这个办公室.
I really have to thank you and Phil, for letting me use this office.
保罗∶嗨!拜托,
Paul: Hey, jees, hey please, don't mention Phil, huh?
不要提菲尔哈!?
He's off at a Zurich conference,
他跑到苏黎士去参加会议,而我却要留在这里看双倍的病人!
and I'm stuck here with a double patient load!
杰森∶至少你不因此而痛苦.
Jason: Ah well, at least you're not bitter about it.
保罗∶很漂亮的家具,对吧?
Paul: Nice furniture, huh?
杰森∶你在开玩笑吧?
Jason: Are you kidding!
保罗∶这些都是我的,只不过我自己的公司把它租来用,
Paul: I own it, but I leased it back to myself, through my own corporation,
可以节省双倍的租金!
for a double rent off!
杰森∶你仍然在学习心理学吗?
Jason: You still practise psychiatry though?
保罗∶很漂亮的椅子,对吧?它可以摆动的!
Paul: Nice chair, huh?It vibrates!
杰森∶哦!我想那是我.
Jason: Oh good, I thought it was me.
保罗∶恩,还要一部固定电话!
Paul: And, it's got a built in phone!
杰森:不需要了.
Jason: No.
保罗∶让我们来看看;你知道看护中心吧,顶上有一个跑道!哇哇哇哇,我得走了,还有2个病人在等着我呢.
Paul: OK, let's see now; You know about the day-care centre, You know there's
a running track on the roof here!Wow wow wow wow wow, I've gotta get
going, I've got two patients waiting for me
杰森∶好,如果这星期太忙,我很愿意伸出援助之手!
Jason: Alright, well if you get swamped this week, I'd be happy to pitch in!
保罗∶哦!我会找你的.
Paul: Oh, I may take you up on that.
杰森∶我们互相敲敲椅子就好了!你好!你好!
Jason: I'll just have my chair call your chair.Hello!Hello!
麦琪:他一定是开玩笑的!泽尔玛,你看到预约单了么?
Maggie: He has got to be kidding!Thelma, have you seen this assignment sheet?
泽尔玛:没有.
Thelma: No.
麦琪∶泽尔玛,是你打印的!
Maggie: Thelma, you typed it!
泽尔玛:是的,但是我没有看.我没有参加.
Thelma: Well yeah, but I didn't read it; that way, I don't get involved.
麦琪∶我想要做一次特刊,"为你们的狗狗的冬天做准备".
Maggie: I'm supposed to do a feature entitled, "Winterizing your dog".
比起给Esquire杂志写那些深刻的,
So, rather than writing an insightful, respectable,
体面的,
journalistic piece for Esquire magazine,
新闻事业的文章,我更愿意告诉人们怎样把雪胎放在他们的指压按磨上.
I'll be showing people how to put snow tyres on their Shiatsus
泽尔玛:好主意.
Thelma: Nice alliteration.
麦琪∶今天我要表明立场.斯德维奇先生,
Maggie: So, this is the day, I take a stand.Mr.
我是一个非常出色的记者,并且我也拼命工作来向你证明这一点,
Sedlovich, I am a darn good reporter,
但是,
and I have worked very hard to show you that,
对于我这个月最大的采访"牙龈炎,你的齿龈是不是在给你一些暗示呢!"
but it's not easy when the biggest story I have done in months is, "
来说,是很不容易的,
Gingivitis, are your gums trying to tell you something!"
老板∶我没能好好的利用你的新闻才能.我要负全部责任,
Boss: I have failed to make use of your journalistic talent.
今天,我要离开这里了.
I accept full responsibility, as of today, I'm out of here.
麦琪∶我不是说你应该辞职!
Maggie: Well, I didn't mean that you had to quit!
老板∶我不是辞职,是被开除了!
Boss: I didn't quit, I'm fired!
麦琪∶你在开玩笑吧?
Maggie: You're kidding!
老板∶是真的,
Boss: No.I'm fired.
我被开除了.
If I were kidding,
如果我是说着玩的话,那我也没必要把我所有的东西都装进这个臭盒子里了.
I would not be packing all of my worldly possessions into this incredibly
你要想我的开心脚吗?
smelly box.Do you want my happy feet?
麦琪∶哦!斯德维奇先生,他们怎么可以这样对你呢?
Maggie: Oh, Mr.Sedlovich, how can they do this to you?
老板∶杂志社经理不喜欢我们的图像,因此我们雇用了一个媒介顾问.
Boss: Station manager's unhappy with our image, so we hired a media consulted.
他来,我就走.
He consulted.I'm gone.
麦琪∶但是这不公平.我们所有的人都要离开吗?
Maggie: But that is so unfair.Well, what if we're all gone?
老板∶麦琪,我觉得比不用担心.
Boss: Oh, I don't think you have to worry, Maggie,
我帮你说了不少好话,当然,
I said some very nice things about you.
我也说了我自己的不少好话,
Of course, I said some very nice things about me too, and look what happened.
还是不管用.我想差不多吧.
Well, I guess that's about it.
Maggie: Mr.Sedlovich, if there's anything I can do, let me know.I mean it
尽管说.
anything.
老板∶我想在报刊新闻学去试试.对了,
Boss: You know, I might take a shot at print journalism again.
That guy from Esquire that keeps calling you, what's his number
麦琪∶哦,是56……等等,我……斯德维奇先生,我可能也需要这个号码.
Maggie: Oh, it's five six five it's...Wait a second, I...Mr.Sedlovich, I may need that number...
老板∶再见麦琪.
Boss: Bye Maggie.
麦琪∶再见锡德.
Maggie: Bye Sid.
老板∶再见,办公室,没有号码,没有脚.
Boss: Bye office.No number, no feet.
迈克∶哦!妈妈,你回来了!
Mike: Oh great Mom, you're home!
麦琪∶哦!你也……
Maggie: Oh you are...
迈克∶我忘记爸爸在上班了,
Mike: Yeah, I forgot Dad was at work,
我还以为要自己准备晚餐了呢.
and I thought I might have to make my own dinner.
麦琪∶见到你也很高兴,迈克.
Maggie: Good to see you too, Mike.
迈克∶妈妈,你今天工作很不开心吗?
Mike: Oh, Mom, you've had a hard day at work, huh?
麦琪,你应该要放轻松,
Maggie listen, you should really ease up,
我是说,你的皱纹又多了几条了.
I mean you're getting some major frown lines.
麦琪∶如果你还想活命的话,你就走开,迈克.
Maggie: If you value your life Mike, back off.
杰森∶哈哈,你好麦琪;你好迈克.
Jason: Ha ha, hello Maggie, hello Mike.
迈克∶爸爸,保重你自己.
Mike: Dad, get a grip on yourself.
麦琪∶看来你今天过的不错.
Maggie: Well you seem to have had a good day.
杰森∶太好了.不知道要怎么来描述,
Jason: Good, doesn't begin to describe it Maggie.I had a great day!!
麦琪.我今天真是太开心了!!我跟你说,
I'm telling you, I had the most fabulous office,
我有一间神话般的办公室,在那里工作的人都棒极了,
the people down there are terrific, and today two...count 'em...
今天,还有2个医生来咨询我关于专业上的事情.我从来都没有这么兴奋过!
two doctors consulted me on their cases.I have never been so excited!
对了,你今天怎么样?
How was your day?
麦琪∶我的老板被开除了,接下来的可能就是我!
Maggie: My boss was fired, and I may be next!
麦琪:杰森,
Maggie: Oh Jason, it's like a morgue down at the station.
像是世界末日了.他们雇用了一个媒体顾问,
They hired a media consulted to change our whole image,
今天他将决定我们的去留.
and today he was deciding who to can.
杰森∶宝贝,对你进行评估不意味着你就一定会被开除呀.
Jason: Oh, honey, just because you're being evaluated doesn't mean you're
他们会认识到你是一个好记者.
going to be fired.You're a good reporter, they're gonna realise that.
麦琪∶对,我是一个好记者.
Maggie: That's true.I am a good reporter.
杰森:还记得金维斯特的故事么!那个可爱的小狗的婚礼!
Jason: Remember that story of Gingivitis, please!!
亲爱的,
And that cute little dog wedding!
那个小猎犬用牙齿咬到花的时候,我哭了!
Honey, when that little beagle caught the bouquet in his teeth, I cried!
麦琪∶哦!杰森!
Maggie: Oh, Jason!!
开萝尔∶你还需要点什么呢;谷物,一个炸面圈,
Carol: Can I get you anything else; cereal, a doughnut,
带佛罗伦萨鸡蛋的荷兰沙司……
eggs Florentine with hollandaise sauce...
法兰克∶不用.
Frank: I'm fine.
开萝尔∶尽管跟我说.
Carol: You're telling me.
杰森:开萝尔,你在做早餐,能给我一个煎蛋么?
Jason: Hi Carol, hey as long as you're fixing breakfast, can I get a scrambled egg?
开萝尔∶爸爸,你想我上班迟到吗?
Carol: Dad, you want me to be late for work!
杰森∶你好,法兰克,
Jason: Hi, Franky, I got a whole new way to go!!!
我有新的想法了!!!你还没有开始做吧?
You don't take suggestions well, do you?
法兰克∶抱歉的.
Frank: Sorry.
杰森∶我只是在想,与其把所有的书架都拔出来,
Jason: Well, I just figured that...err...
还不如放点东西进去……我不知道该怎么说,就是整面墙的日本风景画.
you know if you're tearing out all these book shelves anyway,
或者是,
why not put in...I don't know...a whole wall of Japanese screens.
把房间的其他地方涂上蓝色/灰度色调,哈?
You know, maybe do the rest of the room in some blue/grey tones, huh?
法兰克:我想我是按小时来收你的钱的.
Frank: I think I should have charged you by the hour.
杰森∶哦,对,我要走了……我的同事们都在等着我呢.我觉得我不能继续呆在这里恶劣,我最好能去办公室.
Jason: Yeah.Well, I gotta run...my colleagues are expecting me.Well I guess I can't put it off any longer, I better get into the office.
麦琪:亲爱的,你不用装作比我差,我很好.
Maggie: Oh, honey, you don't have to fake being down for me, I'm fine.
杰森∶真的?
Jason: You sure?
麦琪∶是,要不然我能做什么呢?根本就不是我能控制的.
Maggie: Yeah, what can I do?It's out of my hands.
杰森∶这才是正确的态度.
Jason: Well, that's a very good attitude.
麦琪∶但是,如果我今天担心的事情真的发生了,而你却过的很开心的话,你今天最好还是假装一下……
Maggie: But, if what I think is going to happen to me happens, and you have another great day...fake your little heart
麦琪∶他们不会开除克劳斯医生的,他是做天气的.克劳斯医生,不是你!
Maggie: They won't fire Dr.Claus, he's being doing the weather for ever.Dr.Claus, not you too!
克劳斯医生∶希望不是.
Dr.Claus: Auf wiedersein.
麦琪∶如果他们真的要这样的话,
Maggie: Well if that's the way they're going to be,
我才不在乎他们是否开除我呢.
I don't care if they fire me.
麦琪∶哦!上帝,我还是希望他们不要开除我.
Maggie: Oh God, I hope they don't fire me.
病人∶可能我在我妻子要出去工作的事情上,态度是错的.
Patient: So, I thought maybe I was wrong about my wife wanting to work.
杰森∶我们终于取得了进展.
Jason: Then, we're making progress.
病人:我采纳了你的建议.我告诉她,你不想再待在家里了.
Patient: I took your advice.I told her, you don't wanna be at home anymore, fine.
杰森:好呀.
Jason: Bravo.
病人∶所以,我已经有3天没有看见她了.
Patient: Haven't seen her for three days.
杰森∶我很抱歉.
Jason: I'm very sorry.
病人∶我才不呢.
Patient: I'm not.I'm just waiting for the day she comes waddling home,
我就等着她夹着尾巴蹒跚的回来.西维尔医生,
with her tale between her legs.Excuse me, Dr.
是你的椅子在响吗?
Seaver, is that your chair ringing?
Jason: Yeah, my secretary will get it.Alright, time's up Mr.
Lapepki, and we'll be
meeting again next week, but that will be back home, at my place
病人∶啊,我知道这个地方太好而不能再呆下去了.
Patient: Ah, I knew this place was too good to last.
杰森∶嗨!凯文,凯文,凯文,你打通了我妻子的电话了吗?
Jason: Hey, Kevin, Kevin.Kevin did you get that call through to my wife?
凯文∶打通了,他们说她正在开会.
Kevin: Yeah, they said she was in a meeting.
保罗∶嗨! Jase,你有空吗?
Paul: Hey, you got a minute, Jase?
杰森∶有,你有什么事?
Jason: Yeah sure, come on in.What is it?
Paul: Well, Phil called from Zurich this morning, he's taken a teaching job there
杰森∶你当真!多好的机会!教书然后想什么时候吃奶酪就什么时候吃.
Jason: Oh, you're kidding!What a great opportunity for him!Teaching and great cheese whenever you want it.
保罗∶对他是个很不错的机会,可是,
Paul: Well, it's a great opportunity for him, but what about me?
对我呢?他抛弃了我,就像在我小时候,
I mean, he's abandoned me, just like my father did when I was a child;
我父亲抛弃我一样;我那时还是个5岁的小孩子呀,是多么脆弱的一个年纪.
I was only five years old, which, as you know, is a very vulnerable age.
杰森∶你爸爸之所以要抛弃你,是有原因的,
Jason: Well there's a reason your father abandoned you, Paul; he hated you!
保罗;因为他不喜欢你!每个人的都不喜欢你!
Everybody hates you!
保罗∶你就是这样对你所有的病人的?
Paul: Is this the way you talk to all your patients?
杰森∶只有当我认为他们在欺骗我时,我才这样.
Jason: Well, I do when I think they're trying to con me about something.
保罗∶难以置信!我们有 20年的友谊,
Paul: Oh, I don't believe this!
大学,和事业关系!
After twenty years of friendship, college, professional relationship!
杰森,你真的认为我对你不够真诚吗?
Jason, do you really think I'd be lessthan honest with you?
杰森∶哦!是!
Jason: Oh yeah!
保罗∶你识穿我了!等等,接下来我们说正经事,你想不想把菲尔的这间办公室租下来?
Paul: OK, you got me!But, wait a second now, here's the deal; how would you like to take over from Phil here?
杰森∶你是认真的?
Jason: Are you serious?
保罗∶很显然你喜欢在这里.你会干的很好的,说说,你到底怎么想?
Paul: Look, it's obvious you enjoy being here.And you'd fit in perfect, come on, what do you say?
杰森∶哦!是个很以外的建议...非常有吸引力的建议.可能我们可以实现我们在午餐的时候所讨论的开免费诊所的想法.
Jason: Oh, well it's a very unexpected offer...a very attractive offer.Maybe we could do something finally about that free clinic idea we had at lunch.
保罗∶绝对地!
Paul: Absolutely!
杰森:这就是我向往的工作环境啊!
Jason: This is exactly the kind of work situation I've always dreamed of!
保罗∶啊杰森,太妙了!
Paul: Ah Jason, fantastic!!
杰森∶我做不到.
Jason: I can't do it.
保罗∶哦!等等,我保证以后再也不拥抱你了.
Paul: Oh wait a second, I promise I'll never hug you again.
杰森∶不是,保罗.我和麦琪有个约定.
Jason: No, Paul I have a deal with Maggie.
我们说好,不管怎么样,
We have always believed that one of us should be there for the kids at
我们其中的一个都必须在家里看小孩.现在是她开始事业的时机了,不是我!
all times.It's her time for career opportunities, not mine!
保罗∶哦,听我说,Jase.
Paul: Oh, come on, give me a break, Jase.
你想想看,你在这里可以挣到很多钱,这个对你家庭来说,
I mean look, you can make a lot of money here,
不是也很重要吗?另外,
and that's important for your family too.
你是家庭的主人,应该由你做主,不是吗?
And besides, you're the man of the house, what you say goes, right?
杰森∶这样的说法带有性别歧视,虽然我也同意,但是还是有性别歧视.
Jason: Well that's a very sexist thing to say...agreeable, but sexist.
Paul: Think Jase, this office can be yours, permanently.Yes, even the chair
杰森∶哦!谢谢,谢谢,谢谢……我不能.
Jason: Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you...I can't.
不,我在家里也很开心,保罗.
No, I'm happy at home Paul.
保罗:你很开心?
Paul: Wait a second, you're happy?
杰森∶我很开心,我很开心,哈哈哈哈!
Jason: I'm happy, I'm happy, ha ha ha ha!
Paul: Jase, are you sure you're not blocking or displacing or repressing
杰森∶不是.
Jason: Yes.
保罗∶是的,你是被迫的.
Paul: Yes, you're repressing.
杰森∶不,我不是.
Jason: No, I'm not.
保罗∶那你就是不得已.
Paul: Well then, you're blocking.
杰森∶不,我不是.
Jason: No, no.
保罗∶是的,你是.
Paul: Yes you are.
杰森∶不,我不是.
Jason: No, no.
保罗∶你是.
Paul: Are too.
杰森∶不是的.
Jason: Am not.
保罗∶你是!
Paul: Are too!
杰森∶不是的,不是的.
Jason: Am not, am not.
保罗∶你不愿意承认而已!!
Paul: Yeah, you just won't admit it!!
杰森∶我不是!我不是!我不是!我不是!
Jason: Am not!Am not!Am not!Am not!
保罗∶杰森是被迫的,被迫的,被迫的,被迫的!
Paul: Jason is blocking, blocking, blocking, blocking!
本∶嗨!迈克,看看这个!
Ben: Hey, Mike check this out!
迈克∶是什么东西?
Mike: What the heck is that?
本∶是激光灯,如果与密林动物的节奏一起跳动的话,就不能被关掉.
Ben: It's a laser light show machine that pulses with a jungle animal rhythm that cannot be denied.
迈克∶本,看太多激光会导致你双目失明的.
Mike: Too much of that laser light Ben, and you'll go blind.
本∶明天的聚会上用的着.
Ben: It's for a party tomorrow.
迈克∶什么聚会?
Mike: What party?
本∶我不能告诉你.对所有的人都要保密,特别是……
Ben: The one I didn't tell you about.The one that's a secret from everybody, especially...
迈克∶爸爸.
Mike: Dad.
杰森∶孩子们好.本,你好!
Jason: Hi guys.Go see Ben.There you go baby.
开萝尔∶我的辉煌的大学二年级就这样结束了.做为大三学生,
Carol: So, that brings us the end of my illustrious Sophomore year.
我会用……来面对我的将来,爸爸,
As a junior, I face the future with...
我对大家友好不说明我是在讨好呀.
Dad, just because I'm being friendly doesn't mean I'm flirting.
是个不错的装饰,放过我吧.
This is a perfectly acceptable outfit, give me a break.
法兰克∶你怎么想?
Frank: So, what do you think?
杰森∶关于什么?
Jason: About what?
法兰克:关于中东战争!关于这个办公室!
Frank: About the troubles in the Middle East!About this office!
杰森∶恩,我知道了,我知道了.只要在这里放日本风景画,就在这面墙上.凯文坐这里.我……
Jason: Oh yes, it's getting there, it's really getting there.I just wish those Japanese screens were over here, you know on this wall, over where Kevin sits.That's where..
法兰克∶凯文是谁?
Frank: Who's Kevin?
杰森∶凯文,是我的秘书.你知道我是做什么的吗?
Jason: Kevin, my secretary.You know what I'm doing?
法兰克:不知道.
Frank: Not a clue.
杰森:我正想把这个房子收拾得像我的办公室.所有的建议都是随意的,
Jason: I'm trying to make this room look like my office at work.
都是无意识的.
All these suggestions that I was making randomly; they're not random,
我总是想,我已经厌倦在这里工作,
that was my subconscious talking.
但是不!
All this time, I thought I was tired of working in this room, no!
我是厌倦了在家里工作.这不说明问题么?
What I'm tired of is working at home.Isn't that something?
法兰克∶呼,我已经晕头转向了!
Frank: Hoo, I'm stunned!
杰森∶我也是,我很高兴自己终于想明白了.呵呵,
Jason: Me too, I'm glad I figured this out.I mean, this changes...nothing.
什么都不用改变.不用,麦琪已经花了15年的时间来照顾孩子们了,
No, Maggie put her career on hold for fifteen years to stay home with
现在该轮到我了.这是我们的约定,对吗?
the kids, now it's my turn.That was our deal, right?
法兰克∶对吧.
Frank: Well...
杰森∶对,没错,
Jason: Yes, right, of course it is!!
当然没错!!但是,你会放过这么一个好的机会吗?
But still, would you pass up an opportunity like this?
杰森∶我认为你不会.
Jason: I didn't think so.
我问你,你认为男人该当老板吗,
Let me ask you this; do you think that a man should be boss,
你认为该男人说了算吗?
do you think what a man says goes?
法兰克:这是性别歧视……虽然很有道理,但是,有性别歧视的因素.
Frank: Well, that's a pretty sexist thing to say...agreeable but sexist.
杰森∶可是我不这样想.我觉得如果麦琪工作的很开心的话...
Jason: Well, I don't feel that way.I feel that if Maggie's happy at her job...
对了,我还不知道麦琪到底工作的开不开心呢.
and by the way, I'm not so sure Maggie is all that happy at her job.
事实上可能马上就不是她的工作了,如果他们要开除她的话!
In fact that may not even be her job any more,
哦,如果麦琪被开除的话,
if they decided who they're gonna fire!
那我不是就可以在外面工作了!!!不,
Ho ho, wouldn't that be something if Maggie got canned!!!
不,我不是这个意思.
No, no, I didn't mean that.
麦琪∶你好,杰森,孩子们在家吗?
Maggie: Hello, Jason, anybody home?
杰森∶哦!亲爱的.
Jason: Oh, hi honey.
麦琪∶亲爱的,你今天过的怎么样?
Maggie: Hi honey, how was your day?
杰森∶恩,既然你问了,
Jason: Well errm, to tell you, since you asked,
那我有些事情想和你谈谈……
there was something I kind of wanted to talk about...
麦琪∶今天绝对地,毫无疑问的,
Maggie: Mine was absolutely, without a doubt, the most...
是我一生中最辉煌,最开心的一天!!
fabulous day of my entire life!!Not only did they not fire me they...
他们不但没有解雇我.他们……你看看19新闻频道的核心人员名单.
You are looking at the core of channel nineteen's new news team.
从现在起,
From now on we're a hard news network,
我们是一档新闻网络,我是他们的一号新闻记者!
and I am their number one hard news reporter!
他们根本没想过要开除我,他们是想和我签一个为期7年的合约!!!
They don't want to fire me, they want to sign me to a seven year contract!!!
杰森∶七年.
Jason: Seven years.
麦琪∶宝贝儿,有什么不对劲?
Maggie: Honey, is something wrong?
杰森∶没有,没有,没有.太奇妙了,真是意外的消息.呼,呼,七年.
Jason: No.No, no, that's fantastic, unexpected news.Ho ho.Seven years.
麦琪:不好意思我打断你了,亲爱的,你想对我说什么?
Maggie: Oh, I'm sorry I cut you off, sweetheart, what was it you wanted to say?
杰森∶呵呵,不能和你的消息相提并论.
麦琪∶七年!!
00:22:22,400
Jason: Well, errm...it doesn't compare to your news. Maggie: Seven years!!